-Charlie  把孩子给我  -你以为你是谁啊 John?
-Charlie. Give me the baby.  -Who the hell are you, John?
Aaron不是你该管的
Aaron's not your responsibility.
他出生的时候你在哪里?
Where were you when he was born?
他被抓走的时候你又在哪里?
Where were you when he was taken?
你不是他爸爸  也不是他家人
You're not his father.You're not his family.
你同样也不是  Charlie
Neither are you, Charlie.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这个岛不是你们的 而是我们的
This is not your island.This is our island.
而你们之所以能生活在这里
And the only reason you're living on it
是因为我们允许你们这么做
is because we let you live on it.
这里就是界线了
Right here, there's a line.
如果你们敢踏过这界线
You cross that line,
那我们之间就不仅仅只是误会了
we go from misunderstanding to something else.
你自己决定  Jack
It's your call, Jack.
Sayid和我说你是个警察
Sayid tells me that you're a cop.
曾经是
I was a cop.
我可以请教你一些事情吗?
Can I ask you something?
说吧
Shoot.
你觉得训练一支军队要多久?
How long do you think it would take to train an army?
这是所有的了?
Is that all of them?
所有6支都在这了
All six of them.
但是只有一盒子弹
Plus one box of ammo.
至少目前我们不用担心弹药会用完
At least we don't have to worry about running out anytime soon.
Jack  很高兴你决定
Jack, I'm grateful that you decided
把所有武器都放在同一个地方
to keep them all in the same place.
这是我从Charlie那里拿来的
I had to take them from Charlie.
是藏海洛英的
His heroin stash.
我想如果他看不到这些
I figured it might have therapeutic value,
会对他戒毒有所帮助
if it ever came to that.
你就打算一直把毒品藏在这雕象里?
You're just gonna leave it all in the statues?
那你打算敲碎这7个圣母玛利亚?
You wanna break seven Virgin Marys,
你自便吧
be my guest.
我很迷信的
I'm superstitious.
John
把密码告诉我
The combination.
我想你问我也许是因为
I'm gonna assume that you're asking me
你担心我会摔下悬崖
because you're worried that I might fall off a cliff or something,
或者你觉得只有一人能进来这里
that it's irresponsible for just one of us to have access to this room,
是很不可靠的
rather than this being
而不会觉得这是你不信任我
an issue of trust.
这岛上有很多悬崖  John
Well, there are a lot of cliffs on this island, John.
好吧   但是我觉得我们应该达成协议  Jack
All right. But I think we should agree, Jack,
如果我们中的任何一人需要进来这里
that if either of us need to open this door,
我们都得与对方商量
we consult each other first.
没问题
Absolutely.
右转到7  左转到33
Right seven, left 33,
再右转到18 你要把它记下来吗?
right 18.You need to write it down?
不用了  我记得住
No. I got it.
好吧
All right.
还有  Jack  你应该考虑下
And, Jack, you may want to consider
把药品也放在这里面
locking the medicine in here, too.
我为什么要那么做?
Why would I need to do that?
看吧  看吧
Well, well.
这是谁要在郊区安家啦
Look who had to relocate to the suburbs.
像个娘们似的
Ain't that just like a woman?
她住着大房子 而你却只能呆在小公寓啊
She keeps the house and you get the cheap-ass apartment.
伙计  我以前觉得这些人都恨我
Man, I thought these people hated me,
不过现在这名头得转给你了
but I gotta hand it to you.
偷走孩子  想要把他淹死?
Stealing the baby and trying to drown it?
你现在成为新的孤立对象了
Now, that's a new low.
连Locke都要打你
You even made Locke take a swing at you.
这就好比让甘地来教训他自己的孩子
Hell, that's like getting Gandhi to beat his kids.
你是不是应该担心一下Jack?
Shouldn't you be more worried about Jack
他正在搜你的帐子
ransacking your tent right now?
什么?
What?
你到底在干什么
What the hell you think you're doing?
这些是你从舱里偷出来的
You stole these from the hatch.
-是你从我那偷过去的  -什么?
-You stole them from me.  -What?
它们是我藏起来的  我只是拿回属于我的而已
They were in my stash.I took back what was mine.
这些是属于我们的Sawyer  是属于大家的
These belong to all of us, Sawyer.To the group.
你那藏东西的地方已经没有了
You don't have a stash anymore.
我是认真的  医生  放下它
Doc, you don't wanna do this.
把这些药片还给我 我会当什么都没发生过
Just give me the pills, we'll forget it ever happened.
你在威胁我?
Are you threatening me?
没有下一次了  医生
Last chance, Doc.
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：wjzhu校对：扣扣
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat 闲逛 七色九天
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
你现在想要什么?
What do you want, right now?
就要你
Just you.
该死
Oh, damn it.
怎么了
What is it?
我开会要迟到了 就是我和你说过的那个会议
I'm gonna be late for that meeting I told you about.
会议?
Meeting, huh?
是的
yeah
如果你还有约会 你直说就是了
You got another date,you can just say so.
我可没本事脑袋里同时想着两个女人
I can only wrap my mind around one woman at a time,
但是我还是满欣赏你的宽宏大量
but I appreciate the permission.
一会就回来  美人
Back in a flash, gorgeous.
你不该看到这些
You weren't exactly supposed to see that.
你没开玩笑吧?
Are you serious?
什么?
What?
这不是真的吧
You're not serious?
你这么巧带了个装满现金的手提箱
You just happen to have a suitcase full of cash,
而正要去拿的时候
and you go to pick it up
锁恰好坏了?
and then the lock just happens to break?
给我
Give me that.
这都不是真的钱
It's not even real.
报纸?
Newspaper?
你在想方设法的骗我钱?
Are you trying to con me?
当我问你要这些钱派什么用场时
What, I ask you what all the money's for
你就编一些投资啊什么的来骗我
and you do some song and dance about an investment or something
然后...然后我就会傻呼呼的说"嘿  我这里还有些钱"
and then I say,"Hey, oh, I've got some money. "
看  都被你看穿了
Look, you got me.
你真行啊
Good for you.
这也没什么
No harm, no foul.
你应该有准备的
You should've done your homework.
和他离婚我什么都没得到
I didn't take anything from him in the divorce.
我不值得你花这么多心思
I'm not even worth your trouble.
我真是无地自容啊
Well, shame on me.
告诉我你是怎么做的
I want you to show me what you do.
让我看看你到底是怎么做的
Show me what you do.What you really do.
什么怎么做?
And what do I do?
告诉我你是怎么骗人的  Sawyer
Show me how to con people, Sawyer.
我喜欢你布置屋子的方式
I like what you've done with the place.
今天不用女仆
Maid's day off.
挪一下好吗?
You wanna move?
我听说Jack拿走了你的止痛药
Heard Jack took your painkillers.
是啊  我想那医生算是把我看成外人了
Guess me and the doc are on the outs.
今年又可以少寄一张圣诞卡了
One less Christmas card I'll have to send this year.
这可能会让你开心一点 我从舱里拿来的
Maybe that'll cheer you up.It's from the hatch.
我知道你在为找不到阅读材料发愁
I know you're hard up for reading material.
就象我想知道怎么剪头发一样
Well, as much as I'd like to learn to "feather my hair,"
在竹筏上我把眼镜弄掉了
I lost my damn glasses on the raft.
能读给我听吗?
You wanna read it to me?
怎么了  你有约会么
What, You got an appointment or something?
就这个了
All right.
"10种可以判断他是否是个敏感男人的方法"
"Ten Ways To Tell If He's A Sensitive Man. "
听上去还不错
This ought to be good.
早上好
Morning.
John
Hey, John.
这就是个敏感男人
Now, there's a sensitive man.
Claire让他睡在那边
Claire asked him to sleep down here.
拜托
Come on.
Locke也只是为了得到他想要的
Locke's got himself needs,
就和其他所有人一样
just like anyone else.
不是所有人都象你一样的  Sawyer
Not everyone is like you, Sawyer.
我想这就是为什么Jack和那个Ana Lulu
Guess that's why El Jacko and Ana Lulu
没叫我参加他们的革命的原因吧
didn't ask me to join their revolution.
怎么  你没听说他们的小军队?
What? You didn't hear about their little army?
看来我不是唯一一个被医生看成是外人的人了
Guess I'm not the only one on the outs with the doc.
伙计
Hey, man.
你要把橙汁放在椰子里然后一起喝下去?
You gonna put the lime in the coconut,drink them both up?
"椰子里的橙汁"?
Lime in the coconut?
一首歌
The song?
你想要说什么  Hurley?
What do you want, Hurley?
我刚才在Rose和Bernard的帐子附近
I'm over at Rose and Bernard's tent...
你知道他是个牙医吗?
Did you know he's a dentist?
他们还隐瞒了其它东西
Well, that's not all he's been holding out on us.
他还收到过Boone从那架挪威的
He picked up Boone's signal
飞机上发出的求救信号
from the Norwegian plane.
是尼日利亚
Nigerian.
好吧  反正他是用这个接收到的
Right. Anyhow,he picked it up with this.
这是个短波收音机 是个非常不错的步话机
That is a short-wave radio.It's a glorified walkie-talkie.
是啊  那你能不能把这蓝线和红线转换一下
Yeah, but can't you switch a blue wire
让它变得更好用些?
with a red wire and make it stronger?
我们试着用飞机的 无线电向外发信号
We tried to send a signal with the plane's transceiver
我们所能收到的就只有
and all we got was
那个法国女人16年前发出的循环信息
the French woman's message on a loop.
我为什么还要费劲弄这个?
Why would I bother?
伙计  我是说  这值得...
Come on, man. I mean, it's worth...
这没什么利用价值 只会浪费时间
It's worth nothing.It's a waste of time.
我只是想让你振作一点
I was just trying to cheer you up, dude.
我不需要
I don't need cheering up.
好吧  对不起 没什么事了
OK, man. Sorry. No problem.
你搞到保险门密码了?
You get the combo?
太棒了
Nice.
你不觉得这样就说服你那伙伴
Didn't think it'd be that easy convincing your pal to give it up.
这对你们来说是好事...
That's the nice thing about you people,
你们还没有太害怕
you're not scared enough.
没有太害怕?
Not scared enough?
这也是为什么不能说服大家都加入我们的原因
Same reason no one'll join the army.
这里的每个人都觉得自己很安全
Everyone around here actually thinks they're safe.
相信我  Ana  没人觉得自己安全
Trust me, Ana, no one thinks we're safe.
那么  Jack...
So, Jack,
密码是什么?
what's the combo?
开个玩笑而已
I was just kidding.
Vincent
你在这里干什么呀?
What are you doing out here?
我的天 还真的下雨了
Oh, man, it's really coming down.
快进来  小妞
Get under here, Freckles!
我喜欢雨
I like the rain.
是啊  我也喜欢 但是只限于里面
Yeah, me too, from under here.
怎么回事?
What the hell?
是Sun
It's Sun.
她还好吗?
Is she all right?
还有呼吸
She's breathing.
找Jack  去找Jack
Go get Jack. Go get Jack.
好的
OK.
发生了什么?
What happened?
Jack在哪里?
Where's Jack?
她还清醒吗?
Was she conscious at all?
-她说过什么吗?  -没  一句话都没说过
-Did she say anything?  -Not a word.
她没事了  她没事了 她很快就会好的
She's OK. She's going to be all right.
你让我来照顾她吧  拜托
You need to let me take care of her,all right? Please.
-你怎么找到她的?  -我听到她在丛林里尖叫
-How'd you find her?  -I heard her scream.
她的手是被绑起来的
She was out cold,and her hands were tied.
她的手为什么被绑起来?
What do you mean her hands were tied?
他们又来了
They're back.
他们说过不会来惹我们的
They said they would leave us alone.
恩  John  看来他们毁约了
They broke their promise.
-我们都还不知道到底怎么回事
-We don't even know what happened.
-这不是明摆着么?
-Do we need to know?
你们在哪里找到她的
Where'd you find her?
就在她自己的小花园外
Just outside her garden.
-我们去看看  -带好枪
-We should take a look around.  -With guns.
不行
No.
不行?
No?
如果我们带着武器
We arm up,
可能会误伤自己人
we're just as likely to shoot each other as we are one of them.
好吧
OK.
我们等Sun醒过来吧 她会告诉我们发生了什么
We'll wait for Sun to wake up.She'll tell us what happened.
然后我们得有所行动
Then we're gonna do something about it.
听上去是个计划
Sounds like a plan.
他们通常不留痕迹
They usually don't leave any trail.
还是得去看一下的
It's worth a look.
我来问你些事情
Let me ask you something.
你想得通这一连串的事情吗?
This whole scenario make sense to you?
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
想一想
Think about it.
首先  她怎么能够逃脱的
First off, how'd she get away?
一个女人是不会有这么大的力气的
Woman doesn't weigh 100 pounds.
她是为她性命而挣扎
She was fighting for her life.
这种情况下人们什么都能做的出...
People are capable of anything...
但是你就没能逃脱
You couldn't get away.
你和Sun玩热油锅生死游戏的话
And you versus Sun,hot-oil death match?
我绝对把钱压你那边
My money's on you, Sheena.
谢谢你对我的信心
Thanks for your vote of confidence.
这是个头套  就象他们套在我头上的一样
It's a hood, just like the one they put over my head.
不  这不是
No, it's not.
这个是黑色的 花纹也不一样
This one's black. Different weave.
细节说明一切  他们都错了
It's all in the details,and they're wrong.
那如果不是那些人  还会是谁呢?
Well, if it wasn't them, then who?
你是说是我们中的人干的?
What are you saying, one of us did it?
谁会想要去袭击Sun?
Who the hell would wanna go after Sun?
除非是想说服大家加入军队...
Not much upside to scaring the crap out of 46 people.
再也不会有其它吓唬全部46个人的理由了
Unless you're trying to con them into joining an army.
这些项链分文不值  Sawyer
Those necklaces are junk, Sawyer.
一个5岁小孩都能看出来
A five-year-old could tell that.
他们是不会看这项链的
They ain't gonna look at the necklaces.
他们只会看这标价
They're gonna look at the price.
细节说明一切  甜心
It's all in the details, Dimples.
那如果我们被抓怎么办?
What if we get caught?
我们不会的
We ain't gonna get caught.
如果有人去报警
Anybody goes to the cops,
他们所能记得的就是
the only thing they're gonna remember
那个男人好像在酒吧里闹过事
is a guy who looks like he's been in a bar fight.
你害怕了?
You're scared, huh?
有一点
A little bit.
这是个好消息  宝贝
Well, here's the good news, baby.
所有人都在害怕
Everybody's scared.
他们最害怕的就是
And the thing they're scared of most
错过机会
is missing an opportunity.
-他们就只有这些了  25块
-This is all they had.
-让我们去街头那家
-Let's try down the street.
你们要这些项链吗?
Hey. You guys wanna buy some necklaces?
-哪里来的?  -还用说么
-Where'd you get them?  -What do you think?
你们要不要?
You want to buy them or not?
见鬼  算了
Forget it.
多少钱?
Hey, how much?
100一根
Hundred a piece.
随便哪根都是?
For any of them?
是的  是的 真是明智
Yeah, yeah. Taster's choice.
我要1200的和1300的
I'll take the $1,200 one and the $1,300 one.
谢谢
Thanks.
等等  等一下  伙计  我也买点
Hey, wait.Wait up, man. I'll buy some of those.
我也买
Yeah, me too.
下周是Dana的生日 送这个最好了
Dana's birthday's next week.
他们喜欢珠宝
They love their jewelery.
500  600  700
Five, six, seven hundred.
脉搏跳的稳定有力
Pulse is good, strong.
你只要好好照看她就行了
You just need to watch her.
她会没事的
She's gonna be OK, man.
她额头的肿块...
That bump on her head,
你觉得是她摔倒造成的 还是有人打她的?
do you think she fell or that someone hit her?
我也不知道
I don't know.
Jack你了解Ana Lucia么?
Jack, how well do you know Ana Lucia?
只是...
I was just...
其它人... 我当时和你都在一起
The Others... I was out there with you.
我听到他们说如果我们离他们远点
I heard that man say if we stayed away,
他们不会来惹我们的
they'd leave us alone.
我们已经离的他们够远的了
We've left them alone,
那么他们为什么要再袭击我们?
so why would they attack us a few days later?
如果不是他们 那会是谁?
If it wasn't them, then who was it?
就象我说的  你有多了解Ana Lucia?
Like I said,how well do you know Ana Lucia?
有些人有兴趣加入了
I got a couple more people interested in joining up.
是吗?  谁?
Yeah? Who?
那个很胖的人
The big guy
就是老和Sayid和Scott在一起的那个
who lives behind Sayid, and Scott.
应该是Steve  Scott已经死了
You mean Steve. Scott's dead.
Scott Steve...
我要说的是  在发生了这事以后
The point is, after what happened,
人们总算是肯有所行动了
people are finally willing to do something.
你今天早上在哪里?
Where were you this morning?
很多地方
Lots of places.
在下雨期间呢
During the rainstorm.
你觉得我和Sun被抓有关系?
You think I had something to do with Sun getting grabbed?
你为什么会有这个念头
Now, where would you get an idea like that?
Jack!
Jack...
Sun醒了
Sun's awake.
你的头怎么样?
How's your head?
还疼吗?  晕吗?
Any pain? Dizziness?
还有点儿
Just a little bit.
还记得什么吗?
Do you remember anything?
Vincent出现时我正在花园里忙活
I was working in my garden, when Vincent ran up.
接着就下雨了
It started raining,
然后有人用袋子套住我的头
then there was a bag over my head,
把我拖走了
and I was being dragged.
-他们有多少人?  -我...
-How many were there?  -I don't...
我什么也没看见
I didn't see anything
我拼命反抗
I kicked and I fought,
玩儿命的跑
and I just ran as fast as I could.
然后我摔倒了...
And then I fell...
枪
Gun.
怎么了
Hey. What's going on?
看来岛上的这些人
Looks like the good folks of Islandtown are about to form a posse,
要准备全副武装了
get themselves armed up.
早料到了
I wouldn't be surprised
要是Jack没有叫你
if Jack didn't find that horse of yours,
他就成了名正言顺的领导者了
start leading the charge in a big white hat.
枪
The guns.
这都是她搞的鬼  就是为了得到枪
This is all her play to get her hands on the guns.
Locke  你得去告诉他  他们要来了
Locke. You need to go and tell him they're coming.
要我去?
I need to tell him?
Sawyer  求你了
Sawyer, please.
然后呢?
So, what's next?
然后?
Next?
下一步呢?
The next play.
我来教你怎么骗
I'll show you the pigeon drop.
我们已经两次得手了
We already did that. Twice.
还有塔尔萨州的那次和鲁克的牌局
And the Tulsa bag scam,and the Looky-loo.
我想干场大的
I wanna do a big one.
你想干场什么大的?
You wanna do a big what?
大的骗局
A big con.
那叫放长线吊大鱼
It's called a long con.
好吧  放长线吊大鱼
OK, a long con.
怎么做?
How does it work?
你得让你的猎物求你做事
It works by getting someone to ask you
让整件事看起来像他们的主意
to do something like it's their idea,
你才是幕后操纵者
Your idea
不过这都没关系
But none of that matters,
因为要做这一切只需要一样东西
'cause the one thing you need for a long con,
而我们没有...
we ain't got.
钱
Money.
我有钱
I have money.
听着  Cassie
Sorry, Cassie. 40
共有帐户上的4万块根本不够
grand in some mutual fund ain't money.
还记得我跟你说过
Remember when I told you that
我离婚时没拿到钱吗?
I didn't get anything from the divorce?
我没说实话
I kind of lied.
有多少没说?
You kind of lied how much?
60万美元
600 grand.
见鬼  乖乖 有那么多钱
Hell, with that kind of money,
咱们都可以去找个小岛  在沙滩上晒晒太阳
let's go find an island somewhere
喝个烂醉如泥
and sit on the beach drinking mojitos till we go toes up.
Sawyer  我一生中第一次
Sawyer, for the first time in my life
真的觉得快活
I'm actually happy.
而这并不是因为我们干的事或是得到的钱
And it's not really about the action or the money.
而是因为和你一起做这些事
It's about doing this with you.
来吧
Come on.
吊一次大鱼
One long con.
然后就去快活吧
And then the mojitos.
我会考虑的
I'll think about it.
到这里来考虑如何?
Why don't you think about it in here?
抱歉打扰你了
Hate to interrupt whatever the hell it is you're doing.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
我在按字母排序
I'm alphabetizing.
对啊  Sun在丛林里被袭击了
Oh, sure. Sun gets attacked in the jungle
你倒在这里
and you figure it's a good time
搞你的杜威十进制系统 真厉害
to start the Dewey decimal system.Good thinking.
有事吗  James?
How can I help you, James?
事实上  John  我是来帮你的
Well, actually, John, I'm here
我是来给你报信的
to help you, give you the heads up.
报信?
Heads up?
看来Jack正在来这儿的路上
Jack's on his way over to open your little gun closet
要打开你的小枪柜  拿他想要的东西
and take whatever he needs.
还不止他一个人这样
You should know he's not alone.
所有人都为那个韩国妞的遭遇震惊了
Whole camp's pretty shook up about what happened to Tokyo Rose.
我猜每个人都想逞一逞英雄
I'm guessing everybody's gonna wanna play cowboys and Indians.
而一旦那些枪被拿出来
And once those guns are out and about,
我看是很难再把它们放回来了
something tells me they ain't never going back in.
你干嘛告诉我这些?
Why are you telling me this?
因为这是整Jack最好的方法
Because it'll piss off Jack.
我要是你
But if I were you,
我会马上改一下密码
I'd change that combination pronto.
可那没用  那只会让他缓缓
But that won't work.The door will just slow him down.
Jack想进来就一定进得来
If Jack wants to get in, he'll get in.
能帮帮我么?
Will you help me?
帮什么?
Help you what?
把枪藏起来
Move the guns.
藏到哪?
Move them where?
好吧  你不相信我?那祝你好运吧
Fine. You don't wanna trust me,lots of luck.
可这里不能没人守着
But I can't leave the hatch unmanned.
好吧
Sure.
你去藏枪  我在这里呆着
You move the guns,
再帮你按那该死的按键
and I'll stay here and push your damn button for you.
他们还要多久才来?
How long till they get here?
那就与我无关了 你看着办吧
Well, that ain't my problem, Hoss. It's yours.
牛肉三明治...
Steak sandwich.
两瓶啤酒
Two beers.
谢谢
Thank you.
给我来瓶啤酒吧
Aw, shucks.You got a beer for me?
你也要么?  找服务员吧
You want one, ask the lady.
好吧  真见鬼 给我来一瓶
Ha! Well, hell, I do want one.
再给我来一盘鸡肉沙拉 只要鸡胸脯肉
And could I get a plate of chicken salad, white meat only,
对了  不要芹菜
and please, God,
千万别放哦  行么  亲爱的?
no celery,OK, sweetheart?
我们这里就是这样做的  亲爱的
That's how we make it here, darlin'.
那么...
So,
你搞定她了吧
tell me you got her.
是的  搞定了
Yeah, I got her.
60万都到手了?
All 600 grand?
到手了
All six.
你爱上她了
You fell for her.
噢  算了吧别开玩笑了
You gotta be kidding me.
-听着  这没什么...  -是我找到那个妞的
-Look, It's got nothing...  -I found that bitch.
她叫Cassidy 我等着你跟她纠缠了六个月
Her name is Cassidy.I waited six months while you played house.
告诉你  我是不会中途撒手不管的...
I ain't doing it.
知道什么让你现在这么蠢么?
You know what's making you stupid?
是你该死的男性荷尔蒙
It's your damn hormones.
你以为你沉浸在爱情中了 可实际不是那样
You think you're in love,but you're not.
老虎斑纹是不会变的  James
A tiger doesn't change his stripes, James.
你是个骗子  跟我一样
You're a con man, just like me.
不管你做什么  这都不会改变
And it's not what you do,it's what you are.
明白么?
Do I make myself clear?
对不起  我下不了手
I'm sorry, man. I just can't do it.
不  你必须得干
No, you're gonna do it.
因为那女的... 根本不了解你
Because that girl, she doesn't know you one bit.
但如果她知道你是谁
But when she finds out who you are,
你的真实身份
who you really are,
她会恨死你的
she's gonna hate your guts.
好好吃你的鸡肉沙拉吧  Gordy
Enjoy your chicken salad, Gordy.
等等  别想现在就走
Wait a minute. You don't walk away now.
你欠我的
You owe me.
你想赖帐么?
You don't wanna pay me?
我会让你好看的  James...
I'll put one in your ear, James.
你和你的妞Cassidy
You and your little friend Cassidy.
你在这里干嘛?
What are you doing here?
就要拿到游戏的高分了
I'm like this close to the high score on Donkey Kong.
说吧  要我做什么?
Now, what can I do you for?
Locke在哪?
Where's Locke?
不知道
I don't know.
他好像说去商店买包烟来着
I think he said something about going to the store for a pack of smokes.
看来 咱们当中有小偷了
Uh-oh.Looks like we got ourselves a theft.
谁来报警?  枪在哪?
Who's gonna call the cops?here are they?
别看我  我只按了个按钮
Don't look at me.I was just pushing the button.
对了  我想这些是你的吧
Oh, yeah. I believe these are yours.
不
No.
John... 枪在哪?
John. Where are they?
你把枪藏在哪了?
You move the guns, Where are they?
我们有协议的
We had an agreement!
是有协议  但Jack  你刚刚违反了
An agreement you were about to violate.
是  我是把枪藏起来了
Yes, I moved the guns.
藏哪里了?
Where?
哪里?
John  藏在哪里了?
Where, John?
你准备把它们交出来么?
Are you going to start handing them out?
有多少?  在谁手上?
How many? Who gets them?
事故总是一桩接着一桩
How much time before there's an accident? Another accident?
教Michael开枪是我犯的错误
I made a mistake teaching Michael how to shoot,
那他现在...
and now he's...
我看凶多吉少
He could be dead for all I know,
那...那是我的错
and that was my fault.
我承认  我负责  所以
Yes, I take responsibility for that, so
我会对枪的事情负责的
I'm taking responsibility for the guns, too.
-John  我需要两把枪
-I want two guns.
-抱歉  Jack  事情只能
-That's the way it's gonna be, Jack.
两把枪 快告诉我它们现在在哪?
Tell me where they are right now!
你把枪给了他?
You gave him the guns?
不  我把枪藏起来了
No, I hid them.
没错  Jack 他和你一样蠢
That's right, Jack.He's as stupid as you are.
你们两都忙着猜忌对方
You were so busy worrying about each
你们都没有注意过我吧
other, you never even saw me coming.
你们给我听好了
So, how about you listen up?
我只说一次
Because I'm only gonna say this once.
你翻我的东西
You took my stuff.
趁我为大家寻找救兵的时候
While I was off trying to get us help,
为了救大家
get us rescued,
你拿走了我的包
you found my stash, and you took it,
分了我的东西
divied it up.
剃须沫  电池  甚至啤酒
My shaving cream, my batteries,even my beer.
接着呢
And then something else happened.
你让这两个家伙
You decided these two boys were gonna
来发号施令
tell you what to do and when to do it.
我可不想再任人摆布了
Well, I'm done taking orders.
我也不想要回我的东西了
And I don't want my stuff back.
剃须沫无所谓
Shaving cream don't matter.
电池也无所谓
Batteries don't matter.
但现在唯一重要的就是
Only thing that matters now
那些枪
are guns.
如果你们也想要一支的话
And if you want one, you're gonna
就来我这儿拿
have to come to me to get it.
你想拷打我了  是吧
Oh, you wanna torture me, don't you?
让大家看看你是多么的文明吧
Show everybody how civilized you are.
来啊
Go ahead,
但是我死也不会把枪给你们的
but I'll die before I give them back.
那时你们就真的无计可施了  不是么?
And then you'll really be screwed,won't you?
伙计们  现在我是这里的头儿了
There's a new sheriff in town, boys.
你们最好习惯一下
Y'all best get used to it.
怎么了?  你去哪儿了?
What's going on? Where were you?
Sawyer  怎么了?
Sawyer, what happened?
-看见那辆黑色轿车了么?  -是谁?
-See that black car?  -Who is it?
-他叫Gordy...我的同伙  -什么同伙?
-His name's Gordy. My partner.  -What partner?
如果两分钟内我不带着那个箱子
If I don't walk out with that briefcase
从前门出去  我们俩都死定了
in two minutes, we're both dead.
怎么了?  那就是跟你做生意的家伙?
That's the guy from the Mercado deal?
根本没有什么生意
There is no Mercado deal!
我早知道你有60万
I knew about the 600 grand you had tucked away from the get-go.
Cass...
你就是我们的大鱼
You were the long con.
你这混蛋...
Son of a bitch.
你去死吧  去死
Go to hell. Go to hell.
过去六个月里我们之间发生的一切
Everything that's happened between us in the past six months,
都是真的
all of it, that was real.
滚  你给我滚
Get out. You get out!
待会儿你想怎么恨我就怎么恨我
You can hate me all you want later,
可现在你得听我的
but right now you gotta listen to me.
他会杀了我们的
He is goona to kill us.
因为我说我不会拿你的钱
'Cause I told him I wasn't gonna take your money.
天哪
Oh, my God.
听着  现在我们得...
Look... Now we...
好吧
OK.
我们接下来应该这么做...
This is what we're gonna do.
我要你从后门走  穿过Evan的院子
Go out back through Evan's yard.
我租了辆车停在那门口
There's a rental car parked out front.
去苏族市
Go to Su city.
去赛奇花汽车旅馆
I want you to check in to the Sage Flower Motel.
就在29号公路旁
It's off Highway 29.
看看电视  喝点东西
Watch TV, have a drink, and wait for me.
等着我  我早上就到
I'll be there in the a. m.
-那时一切就结束了  -让我稍微收拾下...
-It'll all be over.  -Let me just pack a few...
没时间了
There's no time.
记得你说过除了我你别无所求么?
You remember when you said I was all you ever wanted?
现在你该体会更深了
Well, now you know better.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
快  快
Go. Go.
你怎么做到的?
How'd you do it?
做什么?
How'd I do what?
Locke说他让你留守
Locke said that he left you in the hatch
他自己去藏枪的
when he went to hide the guns,
而且谁都知道你根本不懂追踪
and we both know you can't track worth a damn.
那么  你是怎么弄到手的?
So how'd you get them?
魔术师永远不会揭自己的底的
Magician never tells his secrets.
你耍我们
You played us.
你还耍了我
You played me.
你说的关于Ana Lucia的一切也是假的...
All that stuff you said about Ana Lucia.
你早知道我会去找Jack
You knew I would go to Jack.
你也知道我会叫你去找Locke
And you knew I'd ask you to go to Locke.
我怎么可能知道那么多
Now how in the world would I know all that?
你有没有对Sun下手?
Did you have anything to do with Sun?
你把我当成什么人了?
What kind of person do you think I am?
我把你当成什么人?
What kind of a person do I think you are?
我看这和枪无关
I don't think this has anything to do with guns,
也和找回你的东西无关
or with getting your stash back.
我看你就是想让人们都恨你
I think you want people to hate you.
还好你不讨厌我  小妞
Good thing you don't hate me, Freckles.
你干嘛非得这么做?
Why do you have to do this?
道高一尺魔高一丈
You run, I con.
老虎斑纹是不会变的
A tiger don't change her stripes.
瞧啊
Hey, check this out.
我在一个箱子里面找到了这份手稿
I found a manuscript in one of the suitcases.
像是一本推理小说
It's like a mystery book.
给你看个东西
I want to show you something.
真酷  你把它修好了
Cool. You fixed it.
看看吧
We'll see.
把这个拿着
Hold onto this.
别抱太大希望
Don't expect anything.
最多也只能收到很微弱的信号
The chances of getting a signal are slim at best.
有噪音就是有戏咯?
Static's good, right?
不  说明接收没问题
No. Reception is good.
听  这是什么?
What's that?
是Rousseau的信号
It's Rousseau's signal.
该死
Oh, crap.
但这个无线电的带宽不错
But this radio has a wider bandwidth.
等等  听到了么?
Oh, wait. Stop. Do you hear that?
那是...
That was...
只是...
Just A-Settin'...
与Cootie同台演出...喇叭...
...Duke Ellington Orchestra,featuring Cootie... the trumpet.
接下来是...
Up next on WXR,
格伦米勒管弦乐队演奏月光小夜曲...
the Glenn Miller Orchestra with Moonlight Serenade.
听啊  多清晰呀
Whoa.You hear how clear that is?
信号很近  对吧?
That's gotta be close, right?
这个波段的无线电信号
Radi1o waves at this frequency
是从大气层电离层反射回来的
bounce off the ionosphere.
可以传几千英里
They can travel thousands of miles.
这个信号可能来自任何地方
It could be coming from anywhere.
或发自任何时间
Or any time.
开个玩笑
Just kidding, dude.
他没注意到你跟踪他  对吧
He never saw you, huh?
没有  他只关心他的破枪
No. He was more worried about his sodding guns than being followed.
根本发现不了
Figured you'd want your friends back.
我想你需要拿回这个  对吧
If I wanted them,
如果我要的话  早就拿了
I would've taken them before
用不着告诉你他们在哪儿
I told you where they were.
我不是为了这个才这样做的
That's not why I did it.
不是么?
It's not, huh?
我就是想让他难堪
I wanted him to look like a fool.
就是想耍耍他
To feel like a fool.
好吧  好吧
Well, well.
看来Johnny Locke是作茧自缚了
Looks like Johnny Locke's got himself a nemesis.
Sun永远也不知道我对她做了什么
Sun can never find out what I did to her.
永远
Never.
别瞎担心了
Don't sweat it.
他们现在有更重要的事情要关心
They got bigger things to worry about now.
Sawyer...
这个主意...
This idea,
所有这些  我们做的这些
all of this, what we did,
你是...
what made...
你是怎么想出来的?
How does someone think of something like that?
现在快走吧
Now, go.
1...
One Mississippi,
2...
two Mississippi,
3...
three Mississippi,
4...
four Mississippi,
5...
five Mississippi...
我不是个好人  Charlie
I'm not a good person, Charlie.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====